<resources>
    <!-- Main Activity Resources -->
    <string name="app_name">Jackson Bottom</string>
    <string name="gps_network_not_enabled">Your GPS is not Enabled. Would you like to turn it on now?</string>
    <string name="open_location_settings">Open Location Settings</string>
    <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="textview_welcome_main">Welcome To The Jackson Bottom Wetland Reserve</string>
    <string name="Is_Your_location_on">Is your location on?</string>
    <string-array name="Rules">
        <item>Trails are open dawn to dusk, seven days a week.</item>
        <item>No dogs or bicycles, please.</item>
        <item>The Education Center is open 10 am to 4 pm, seven days a week</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="button_launch_virtual_tour_text">Take the Virtual Tour</string>

    <!-- Map Markers Resources -->
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="marker_jackson_main">Jackson Bottom Wetlands</string>
    <string name="marker_upland_ponds">Upland Ponds</string>
    <string name="snippet_upland_ponds">These ponds were made by people but the animals quickly moved in.  You can see small tadpoles and fish along the warm edges.  Look carefully and you may be able to see a bullfrog lurking in the shallows as well.  Bullfrogs are not native to this area but love to eat the tadpoles and other creatures in these ponds.  If the bullfrogs jump you may hear them make a funny “squeak” sound.</string>
    <string name="marker_bee_boxes">Mason Bee Boxes</string>
    <string name="button_launch_map_text">Open Map</string>
    <string name="snippet_bee_boxes"><![CDATA[<p>The large house like boxes you see are homes for Mason Bees.
        These bees don\'t make honey and they don\'t sting but they do a great job of pollinating all
        the flowers you see around you.</p><p>The bees emerge from their cocoons in the spring. They build
        a nest in narrow holes.</p><p>Females visit flowers to gather pollen and nectar. The bee lays an
        egg. Then, she creates a wall of mud, which doubles as the back of the next cell. The
        process continues until she has filled the cavity.</p><p> By the summer, the larva has
        consumed all of its provisions and begins spinning a cocoon around itself.</p>
        <h2>Questions:</h2>
        <ul><li><strong><em>How many of the tubes in the houses look like they are full?</em></strong></li>
        <li><strong><em>If you were a bee which flowers in this garden would
        you like best?</em></strong></li></ul>]]></string>
    <string name="fade_in">Fade In Tiles</string>
    <string name="transparency">Transparency</string>
    <string name="button_launch_tile_overlay_text">Test Tile Overlay</string>
    <string name="text_marker_title">Explore Jackson Bottom</string>
    <string name="wv_marker_description"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Welcome to the Jackson Bottom Wetlands Virtual Tour</strong>.</p>
        <p>To begin your tour, select any of the markers below to learn more about the area.</p>]]></string>

    <!--    Permissions    -->
    <string name="permission_rationale_location">Access to the location service is required to demonstrate the \'my location\' feature, which shows your current location on the map.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_denied">This sample requires location permission to enable the \'my location\' layer. Please try again and grant access to use the location.\nIf the permission has been permanently denied, it can be enabled from the System Settings &gt; Apps &gt; \'Google Maps API Demos\'.</string>
    <string name="permission_required_toast">Location permission is required for this demo.</string>

    <!-- Other -->
    <string name="map_not_ready">Map is not ready yet</string>
    <string name="text_marker_title_error">Not There Yet</string>
    <string name="text_marker_description_error">Sorry, it\'s the students\' job to finish this.</string>
    <string name="marker_overlook_fence">Overlook Fence</string>
    <string name="button_launch_web_photos">Photo gallery</string>


</resources>
